Jennis Marie Vicente-Feliciano

Fully bilingual Data Analyst and former manager, researcher, and writer whose experience makes the perfect combination to take on any challenge as a data scientist.

Using technical skills to make an impact on a company or the world.

Passionate about learning and innovating; acquiring skills while collaborating with a like-minded team to reach results.

EDUCATION

2021 INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF **INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY**

Bangalore, India
Executive PGP in Machine Learning &

Python, Advanced SQL, Data Analysis in Excel,

Statistics and Exploratory Data Analysis, Machine Learning (I,II), Natural Language Processing, Deep Learning, Reinforcement Learning

LIVERPOOL JOHN MOORES UNIVERSITY Liverpool, UK

MSc in Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence

Research Methodologies, Dissertation

UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA

Phoenix, AZ

Data Analytics Certificate
Excel VBA, Python, SQL, MongoDB, HTML, Java,
Matplotlib, Leaflet, Flask, Heroku apps

COLUMBIA COLLEGE

Columbia, MO

Business Management Coursework Principles of Management, Organizational Management, Human Resources Management, Business Law I, Business Law II

UNIVERSITY OF MISSOURI

Columbia, MO

Mechanical and Nuclear Engineering Coursework

Coursework in Mechanical and Nuclear Engineering. Research in Nuclear Engineering

UNIVERSIDAD POLITÉCNICA DE **PUERTO RICO**

San Juan, PR

Mechanical Engineering Coursework

FSAE Competition. Secretary in the Student

ABILITIES

- Blilingual (English/Spanish)
- Simultaneous Interpretation (English/Spanish)
- Produce a tangible, positive impact
- Focus on results
- Display strong analytical qualities Maintain effective cost control
- Resource Maximization
 Displays excellent intuitive judgement
- Strive for the achievement of excellence
- Polished and confident speaker

Located: Phoenix, AZ 85007 Phone: (573) 355-0173

Email: jennis.m.vicente@gmail.com

Professional Social Media: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jennisvicente/

Software Development: https://github.com/jennisvicente

TECHNICAL SKILLS

R | SQL | MongoDB | Microsoft Word | Excel /VBA | Python | Pandas | Tableau | JavaScript | Big Data | Machine Learning | Git MySQL | HTML | Al | Web Scraping | Data Mining | ArcGIS

EXPERIENCE

KELLYOCG, Phoenix, AZ

Manufacturing Tech/ Shift 1 Lead June 2020 - August 2021

Bay Captain Certified October 2020 PGV Certified June 2020 SALT Certified August 2020 SALT/ASH Project Lead August-September 2020 Work in a clean room environment abiding and enforcing safety rules and regulations

Extensive knowledge of fully automated manufacturing processes.

Assess, plan, organize and lead a team to manually continue production while automation is interrupted.

Plan training and certification for new hires as well as monthly audits. Report any safety concerns using the appropriate channels if they can't be immediately resolved.

Ensure our tools are in working order or sent to repair.

DATA SCIENCE CONSULTANTS, LLC, Mesa, AZ

Chief Executive Officer, Founder November 2019 - Present

Data analysis and Data Visualizations: https://www.eq-tracker.xyz/, https://www.grabandgoAZ.info, Data Consultant, Assistant Project Manager, Data Visualizations and centralization of embedded resources from other websites: https://www.3CoPR.com

JAEMV, LLC, Mesa, AZ

Writer, Proofreader July 2017- Present

Freelancer- legal research and development of statements to support cases, editing and proofreading opening and closing statements. Business strategist and development and implementation of business

plans.

WALMART, Maricopa, AZ

Assistant Manager November 2007 - August 2019

Promoted adaptability to company guidelines to increase profit by 10% over the previous year in apparel. Increased profitability by creating a "Can it be sold" mentality, trained and implemented a system to reduce markdowns to zero in apparel merchandise, eliminating the need to use extra hours before the yearly store inventory and keeping accurate on hands throughout the year. Making deposits and document cash shortages. Coaching and training the associates in the store. Resolve customers' issues efficiently and quickly. Work at the cash registers when needed to decrease the waiting time of the customers.

the customers,

Meet sales and growth goals set by the management.
Deal with loss prevention to lessen shrink.
Assist the store manager as requested.
Top Sales Increase YoY on Black Friday 2018- Nov 1, 2018, Market 373
Highest Usage of COWM on Market for week 43-Nov 1, 2018
2nd on Sales on Region on Black Friday 2018
Top lottery sales in WM Supercenters in AZ- September 1, 2018